var questions_java=[{
    "question":"This is the parent of Error and Exception classes",
    "option1":"Throwable",
    "option2":"Catchable",
    "option3":"MainError",
    "option4":"MainException",
    "answer":"1"

},{
    "question":"Which of these keywords is used to define packages in Java?",
    "option1":" pkg",
    "option2":"Pkg",
    "option3":"package",
    "option4":"package",
    "answer":"3"
},
    {
        "question":"Which of these is a mechanism for naming and visibility control of a class and its content?",
        "option1":"Object",
        "option2":"Packages",
        "option3":"Interfaces",
        "option4":"None of the Mentioned",
        "answer":"2"
    },
    {
        "question":"What is Package?",
        "option1":"Package defines a namespace in which classes are stored.",
        "option2":"A package can contain other package within it.",
        "option3":"Java uses file system directories to store packages.",
        "option4":"A package can be renamed without renaming the directory in which the classes are stored.",
        "answer":"4"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of these keywords is used to define interfaces in Java?",
        "option1":" interface",
        "option2":"Interface",
        "option3":"intf",
        "option4":"Intf",
        "answer":"1"
    },{
        "question":"Which of these can be used to fully abstract a class from its implementation?",
        "option1":"Objects",
        "option2":" Packages",
        "option3":"Interfaces",
        "option4":" None of the Mentioned",
        "answer":"3"

    },{
        "question":"Which of these keywords is used by a class to use an interface defined previously?",
        "option1":"import",
        "option2":"Import",
        "option3":"implements",
        "option4":" Implements",
        "answer":"3"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of the following is correct way of implementing an interface salary by class manager?",
        "option1":" class manager extends salary {}",
        "option2":"class manager implements salary {}",
        "option3":"class manager imports salary {}",
        "option4":"None of the mentioned",
        "answer":"2"
    },
    {
        "question":" Which of the following methods is a method of wrapper Integer for obtaining hash code for the invoking object?",
        "option1":" int hash()",
        "option2":"int hashcode()",
        "option3":"int hashCode()",
        "option4":"Integer hashcode()",
        "answer":"3"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of these is wrapper for simple data type char?",
        "option1":" Float",
        "option2":"Character",
        "option3":"String",
        "option4":"Integer",
        "answer":"2"

    }];
